<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>HTB on CS&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/tags/htb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HTB on CS&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:08:29 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/tags/htb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nibble [HTB Walkthrough]</title>
      <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/nibble/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:08:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/nibble/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge Gained 🙉  sudo gobuster   Enumeration First, we start off a rustscan scan and the scan returned 2 open ports, port 22 SSH and port 80 HTTP.
rustscan -a 10.10.10.75 I visited the HTTP server and its just a empty page with one line of text.
I then checked the source code of the website and found that theres a line of commented code pointing to /nibbleblog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netmon [HTB Walkthrough]</title>
      <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/netmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 21:04:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/netmon/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge Gained 🙉  psexec Windows File System   Enumeration First off, we scan the machine and noticed a lot of ports opened. WinRM (Windows Remote Management) is a Microsoft protocol that allows remote management of Windows machines over HTTP(S) using SOAP. On the backend it&amp;rsquo;s utilising WMI, so you can think of it as an HTTP based API for WMI.
I first start off with the ftp server and check if the server allows anonymous acces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cap [HTB Walkthrough]</title>
      <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 19:08:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/cap/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge Gained 🙉  GTFObins wireshark capabilities   Enumeration First we did a rustscan + nmap scan, which found 3 ports, SSH, FTP, and HTTP.
rustscan -a 10.10.10.245 Next I run gobuster to find sub directories for the website. Nothing much is interesting.
gobuster dir -u http://10.10.10.245 -w /usr/share/wordlists/dirbuster/directory-list-2.3-medium.txt -t 100  Foothold When I browse around the website, I noticed that the only one interesting page is the data page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor [HTB Walkthrough]</title>
      <link>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 14:38:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tylerwcs.github.io/blog/posts/third/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge Gained 🙉  LFI and Directory Traversal gdbserver screen rustscan wpscan   Enumeration In this machine, I learned a new way to scan for open ports, that is using rustscan. It took less than few seconds for it to find the ports open and it also runs nmap automatically. The scan shows that we have 3 open ports running, port 22, 80 and 1337.
First I took a look at the port 80 website, it shows that it is a website built using Wordpress, therefore we can run wpscan to enumerate more infos about the website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
